<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ben&#39;s Nurture Africa Trip</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ben&#39;s Nurture Africa Trip</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 20:21:40 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10km for 10 Days: Day 3</title>
      <link>/posts/10kday3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 20:21:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/10kday3/</guid>
      <description>Day 3 was tough.
A warm Wednesday did contribute to the toughness but general fatigue was the main culprit. Like I said in the video below, me being uncomfortable for 2 hours a day for 10 days really in nothing in the grand scheme of things.
I love getting out and doing this, it&amp;rsquo;s a really good way of combining something I am pationate about with something I want to get better at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10km for 10 Days: Day 2</title>
      <link>/posts/10kday2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:12:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/10kday2/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday, 16 May 2023 was day 2 of running 10 kilometers for 10 days in a bid to raise as much money and attention for Nurture Africa. Lovely warm day made the run pleasant but also made it harder. The added 10 minutes in the sea starts out with me being a stuttering mess and within 1 minute being calm and enjoying the cold.
To the people who have donated so far, THANK YOU, from the bottom of my heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10km for 10 Days: Day 1</title>
      <link>/posts/10kday1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 16:52:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/10kday1/</guid>
      <description>Today(Actually yesterday at day of publication) marks day 1 of my first fundraising venture for my return to Uganda. I will be writing a blog like this everyday for the next 10 days and posting my journey while over in Uganda. The idea of this blog is not only to raise money for this trip but to drive traffic to this website so I can convince companies to sponsor tshirt/hoodie space AND so you can see the work Nurture Africa do in Nansana.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
